faithfulprovisions.com 2010-12-27

# Privacy Policy

Don't miss a deal, [subscribe to Faithful Provisions daily email](http://bit.ly/wwsgdfeedburner). Use my [Category Page](http://bit.ly/wwsgdcatpg) to help you find what you are looking for. New to couponing? Check out my [Getting Started](http://bit.ly/wwsgd-gettingstarted) page. Thanks for visiting!

Your privacy is very  important to me and I will respect the information that you submit to me in order to enter the giveaways that I host or subscribe to on Faithful Provisions (Hancock Group LLC). This blog does not collect information from minors, only from adults ages 18 and above. I will never give or sell your email address to anyone. This blog is hosted by Uncorrupted, and their privacy policy is [here](http://uncorrupted.net/legal/).

In general, you are responsible for the information you submit in the form of a comment on a post. Your comments can be read by anyone and your profile can be viewed by anyone. I do allow you to post comments as “Anonymous” as a way to help protect your privacy. This blog uses Google Docs forms in order to collect information from readers for giveaways and surveys. I do not give the information you submit to giveaway sponsors or anyone else. Your first name may be shared on this blog if you win a giveaway, but your email address and full name are always kept private and not shared with anyone else unless I have your express permission.

This blog uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Faithful Provisions (Hancock Group LLC). These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) to visit the Google Privacy Center.

Here is information on the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Faithful Provisions (Hancock Group LLC), and how we safeguard your information.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Faithful Provisions (Hancock Group LLC) to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/)

Please contact me by email if you have any questions about these policies.
